In this exercise, you are asked to create
在此练习中 将要求您创建
a DynamoDB table and then transform that table into a global table.
动态数据库表 然后将该表转换为全局表
You can see here we've created a DynamoDB table with has some basic details, table name.
您可以在这里看到我们创建了一个 DynamoDB 表 具有一些基本详细信息 表名
Then we set up our primary partition key.
然后 我们设置了主分区键
Then we have also enabled streaming on the table,
然后我们也在桌子上启用了分流
which is a requirement for global tables.
这是对全局表的要求
We move down to our Global Table's tab.
我们向下移动到 " 全局表 " 选项卡
We can see that we now have the option to add a region to our table.
我们可以看到 我们现在可以选择在我们的谈判桌上增加一个区域
We add the region by selecting whichever region where we'd like to replicate to.
我们通过选择我们希望复制到的区域来添加区域
AWS tells us that that region is ready and available,
AWS 告诉我们那个地区已经准备好了
and we create a replica.
我们创造了一个复制品
Once this finishes, we'll have a global table that is
一旦完成 我们将拥有一个全局表 即
writable in multiple regions, and there we go.
在多个区域中可写入 并且存在